Guide to the Adelaide Bean Papers TAM.756
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. Theatrical Work, 1923-1997
  - The Common People with Anita Satisfield in concert, August 26, 1972 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_054)
  - Artists' Ad-Hoc Committee for Chile, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Lester Cole - Play Manuscripts and Drafts, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7, 8)
    Includes drafts for the following plays:
    The Athenian Connection, 1974; This Time Yesterday, n.d.
  - Actors' Equity Association, Chicago, 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Mike Davidow - Play Manuscripts and Drafts, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10, 11)
    The Closest Battlefield, 1975; Farewell Fanya, n.d.
  - Actors' Equity Association - Showcase Code, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Zero Mostel, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - SAG-AFTRA Strike - Actors' Equity Association Support, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Actors' Equity Association - John Van Eyck, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sean O'Casey Centennial - Correspondence with Robert Lowery and Working Papers, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5, 6)
  - Lester Cole - Correspondence, Drafts, Press, 1978-1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Paul Robeson - Memorial Events and Productions, 1978-1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Musicians Local 802, 1978-1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - AFTRA Twin Cities Local - Newsletters, Notes, and Press, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ringling Bros. / Barnum and Bailey Contract with Local No. 688, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fringe Benefits: KAXE FM, Grand Rapids, MI, February 12, 1983 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_055, 756_072)
  - Little Flags Theatre: To the People, Step in Time, 1983 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_056)
  - Terence Cannon - Play Manuscripts and Drafts, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 3, 4, 5, 6, 7)
    The Captain, n.d.; The Marriage, 1984; The Quarry, 1986; Sand, n.d.
  - Unions for the Performing Arts - Flyers, c. 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Howard Da Silva - Bio and Obituary, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Barrie Stavis - Correspondence and Press, 1986-1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Coming On Strong: Songs for People on the Move, 1987 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_077)
  - Paint the Town Red: Party Songs, 1987 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_078)
  - Prophets: Meira (Chaconne) and Piano Sonata No. 3 Outeries / Black Snow by Ron Yedidia, July 11, 1989 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_073)
  - SAG-AFTRA New England - Newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Catherine Sanford - Correspondence and Drafts, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - SAG-AFTRA Philadelphia - Correspondence, Newsletters, Press, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - AFTRA SIXTY Gala, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - AFTRA E-mails, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Ballad for Americans, Undated (Box 37, Reel 756_039)
  - Barrie Stavis, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_001)
  - Bernice Diskin - Drafts and Correspondence, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Bernice Diskin, Barrie Stavis, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_008)
  - Billie Holiday, Undated; cuid43006 (Box 36, Reel 756_029)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 40 minutes
  - Bless the Child, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_004, 756_005, 756_006, 756_007, 756_009, 756_010, 756_011, 756_014)
  - Born to Live - Studs Terkel, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_034)
  - Brandenburg Concerts - Prokofiev (#2 in F Major, #3 in G Major), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_022)
  - Crane, Undated (Box 35, Reel 756_024)
  - A Dance Suite for Children by Norman Curtis, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_003)
  - Demaio Tribute, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_062)
  - Fayette County: My Name is Georgia Turner, Undated (Box 37, Reel 756_042, 756_043, 756_045)
  - Film criticism: Lester, Bonasky, Hart, etc., Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_063)
  - Fred Pinkard [?] - Paul Robeson, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_036)
  - The Hill Mitschnilt, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_030)
  - Horace Payton (?), Undated (Box 37, Reel 756_044)
  - If We Grow Up (Monophonic), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_017)
  - The Imaginary Invalid, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_020)
  - Irma Jurist: Hymn-like "Wasp" (poor recording), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_015)
  - Jimmy Boy, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_002)
  - Joe Hill by Barrie Stavis - Info Sheets and Flyers, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Juno (TV News and Weather), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_035)
  - Kenneth White - Play Manuscripts and Drafts, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5, 6)
    Airman, n.d.; Discovering Connecticut, n.d.
  - Leo and Kathy Lara: Ecuador, Minneapolis, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_061)
  - Lily (Part 1), Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_063)
  - Mime Troupe, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_057, 756_058)
  - Mother Courage, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_023)
  - No for an Answer Marc Blittzstein, Undated (Box 36)
  - Paul Robeson, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_065)
  - Paul Robeson: The Four Rivers (V. Gorney, E. Elison, H. Meyers), Undated (Box 35, Reel 756_027)
  - Paul Robeson Tributes: Dr. Hasbrouch, Hazel Gray, Dick Herbert, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_018)
  - Preamble to Peace (with intro and applause), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_016, Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 3)
  - Recession-Depression by Barbara Ford, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_064)
  - "Song of Peace" by Shostakovich (Moscow Concert), Undated (Box 35, Reel 756_025)
  - Strange Fruit Musical Score by Lewis Allan, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Studs Terkel: Almanac - Emanuel Dunn, Undated (Box 37, Reel 756_040, 756_041)
  - Studs Terkel's Program on Marc Blitzstein, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_019)
  - Songs of Experience (For Norman), Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_032)
  - Weavers, Pete Seeger, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_031)
  - William Blake's Songs of Innocence set to music by Norman Curtis, Undated (Box 36, Reel 756_037, Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_012, 756_013, Box 36, Reel 756_021, 756_028, 756_033, 756_038, Box 37, Vhs 756_079, Reel 756_048, Reel 756_026)
- Series III. Journalism, 1938-1998
  Series III. Journalism, documents Bean's career as a journalist and editor. These materials are from her early work as a market researcher, her work as co-editor of Labor Today from 1971-1974, and her tenure as arts editor of The People's Daily World from the late 1970s to 1980s. It also includes the works of her journalist, writer, and poet colleagues, including Meridel Le Sueur, Walter Lowenfels, and Art Shields. Much of this work is related to the Communist Party and labor issues in subject matter.
  - Clarity, a Publication of the New York State Communist Party, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Theatre Arts Committee Magazine, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 2, 3)
  - John Donar: Common Man by Walter and Elizabeth Rogers, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee to Lift Ban on The Nation, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Equity Magazine, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Committee to Defend V. J. Jerome, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Theatre Arts Magazine, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - American Voices by Walter Lowenfels (Draft with Annotations), circa 1958 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Walter Lowenfels - Publications, Drafts, 1959-1976 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Mark Rogovin and Public Art Workshop - Correspondence and Works, 1962-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Earl Robinson - Correspondence and Works, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Post Magazine, including After the Fall by Arthur Miller, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - American Dialog Journal, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Adelaide Bean's Market Research, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - American Dialog Journal, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Biological Warfare: Is It Coming?" by Theodor Rosebury, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Labor Today, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Second City, circa 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Who is Lenin? Americans Respond" by Walter Lowenfels, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Labor Today, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Alienation and Dialectical Logic" by Harry K. Wells, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Labor Today, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6, 7)
  - Labor Today, 1972-1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - West End Journal, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Reporter Journal, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Canto Libre Magazine, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Gus Hall about starting at the Daily World, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Frederic Rzewski - Music and Writing, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Labor Today Goodbye Party for Adelaide Bean, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Walter Rogers, Elizabeth Rogers, and Victory Library - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Graphic Arts Worker, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Toward Revolutionary Art Magazine, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Labor Today, 1975-1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Received while Working as Editor at the Daily World, 1975-1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Daily World Bicentennial Calendar, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Daily World on the Death of Paul Robeson, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Black Liberation Journal, National Magazine of the Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Daily World Correspondence and Submissions, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Richard Davidson - Poetry, 1976-1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Correspondence Magazine, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Political Affairs, Theoretical Journal of the Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA), 1977-1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Daily World Working Papers and Correspondence with Robert Hart, 1977-1986 (Box 24, Folder 5, 6)
  - Daily World Correspondence and Submissions, 1977-1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Art Shields - Correspondence, Publications, Memorial Event Programs, 1977-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Tricontinental, Journal of the Organization of Solidarity of the Peoples of Africa, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - World Student News Magazine, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Anton Refregier - Correspondence and Artwork, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sez Journal, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Subtext Newsletter, 1978-1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Daily World Working Papers and Correspondence with Robert Hart, 1978-1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Something of My Life by Luis Corralan with Preface by A. Hanson, and Correspondence with A. Hanson, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Labor Today, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Labor Today, 1979-1983 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Terry Cannon - Drafts and Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Labor Today, 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Quindaro Magazine, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Thomas McGrath - Correspondence, Publications, Memorial Event Program, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Meridel Le Sueur - Profiles, Works, and Event Programs, 1980-1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Daily World, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 10, 11)
  - Talkin' Union Journal, 1981-1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ernest De Maio - Works, Memorial, 1981-1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Art Shields, John Weir, and Esther photograph, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Party Builder Bulletin, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Poems by Prairie, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Twin Cities Cultural Worker, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - American Theatre Magazine, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Mountain Voice Newsletter of the Appalachian South Folklife Center, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Anya Achtenberg - Correspondence and Poetry, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Dramatics Magazine, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Clarence Kailin - Works, Tributes, Socialist Dialogue, 1986-1995 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Political Affairs Journal, 1987-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Vernon Pedersen - Correspondence and Drafts of Russian Reds and Radical Roustabouts, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Equity News, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cuba Action Newsletter, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Nezavisimaya Gazeta from Russia Newspaper, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Committees of Correspondence Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Dialogue and Initiative Journal, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Native American Rights Fund Legal Review, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Committees of Correspondence Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Allegro: Associated Musicians of Greater New York Local 802 Newspaper, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - The Volunteer Journal of the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Oral History Notes, circa 1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Art Shields - Book drafts, Undated (Box 27, Folder 11, 12)
  - Black Liberation Journal, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - For the Revolution Poems by Stuart McCarrell, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Norman Roth Poetry, Undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Meridel Le Sueur Photostrip, Undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Series IV. Subject Files, 1926-1995
  Series IV. Subject Files, includes materials collected by Bean on a variety of topics includes materials that Bean collected on a variety of topics related to labor organizing, theater, and communism.
  - 100 Anos - O Orvalho, 1976 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_075)
  - AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Albert Maltz on Edward Dmytryk, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - American Crusade to End Lynching, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - American Peoples Tribunal Proposal, Undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Black Performing Arts in the U.S. - News Clippings, 1976-1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Blacklisting in the Television Industry, circa 1950-1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Buenavetura, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_067)
  - Carol Graves, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_068)
  - Chicago - Art Events, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Typographical Union - Newsletters, Correspondence, and Press, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Chilean Theater and the Pinochet Dictatorship, 1973-1990 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Committees of Correspondence - Working Papers, Publications, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Communist Hunger March of 1932, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Communist Party of Schenectady, New York, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Communist Party of New York State, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) - 25th National Convention, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) and the Afro-American Struggle - Publication and Discussion Guide, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) and the Arts - Reports, Meeting Minutes, Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) - Campaigns and Working Papers, 1979-1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) - Reports and Basic Documents, 1983-1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions - Cultural and Scientific Conference for World Peace, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cuba - ABC Project, Outlined by KPS and Mary Murray, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_074)
  - Cuba - U.S. Trade Embargo, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Cuban Theater and Politics, 1975-1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Centralism - Notes and Reading, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Theodor Rosebury - Obituary, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Defense Fund - Annual Report and Newsletters, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Ernest Demaio: Nixon Economics, May 15, 1971 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_066)
  - Ernest Hemingway on the Spanish Civil War, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Free Angela Davis, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - French Communist Party - Published Articles, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Future of the Communist Party - Collected Readings, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - German Democratic Republic, Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Government Subsidy for the Arts, 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Gus Hall, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_071)
  - Gus Hall - Communist Party of the United States of America (CPUSA) Speeches, 1971-1983 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Harry Gottlieb Interview in "The New Common Good", 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Henry Winston - Published Lectures, 1951-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - House Committee on Un-American Activities, 1948-1953 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hugo Gellert - Events and Press, 1981-1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Inequality in Theater and Entertainment - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical and Stage Employees (IATSE) and National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET) Merger, 1980-1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - International Federation of Actors - History, 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - International Longshoremen's Association - Racism, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Joe Hill - Anniversary of Death, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Joe Slovo on Socialism in South Africa, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - John Brown, 1970-1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - John Burns UFWOC 305/633-7071, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_068)
  - Julie Kailin on Anti-Racist Education, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Labor Disputes in the Entertainment Industry, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - League of Professional Groups for Foster and Ford: "Culture and the Crisis", 1932 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Legislation Affecting the Arts, 1977-1986 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Martinville Seven, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - McCarren-Walter Immigration Act, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Michael Parenti: "Media, Third World, the Cold War" at Macalester College, Minnesota, February 26, 1987 (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_069)
  - Milan Stephens, Ernie Demaio, Catherine Floris [?], Undated (Box 37, Reel 756_046)
  - Miners' Strike, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Monopolization of Media Industries, 1975-1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Mordecai Gorelik "On Brechtian Acting", 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - National Negro Congress, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - National Theatre of the United States, 1945-1975 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - National Writers Union, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Native American Music and Colonialism - Readings, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - New York State Senate Recommendations and Observations on the Culture Industry, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - News Media Union Mergers, 1975-1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Pablo Neruda - Event Programs, 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - President Roosevelt's Birthday Greeting, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Racism in Manufacturing Plants - Research, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Racism in Performing Arts, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Ralph Fasanella, Folk Artist, 1952-1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Reaganism and the Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Renewal of the Communist Party - Readings, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Research on Funding for the Arts, circa 1969 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Russian Revolution - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "Senefer and Hatshepsut" Study Guide by Beatrice Lumpkin, Undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Single-Payer Healthcare, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Skip Schiel - Photography Exhibits, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Slavery and Thomas Jefferson, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Smith Act, 1950-1952 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - South and Central America - Theater and Human Rights Struggles, 1976-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Soviet Union - Arts and Politics, 1943-1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Struggle Against Racism in the Arts, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Study Guides on Communist Theory, 1926-1947 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Tecla Artwork - "The People of Yes," Uptown Beat Literary Quarterly, 1968-1972 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 2)
  - "Ten Days in Nicaragua Libre", Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Theatrical Transportation, Undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy - Leaflets by Peggy Lipschutz, 1972-1975 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy - Illinois Rank and File Conference, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy - National Coordinating Committee Posters and Literature, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Twin Cities Newspaper Guild - Election of John Kailin, 1973-1989 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America - CIO, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - United States Subic Naval Base in the Philippines, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Vietnam War - Antiwar Events, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Vietnamese Literature - Compilation of Research, 1974-1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Vladimir Lenin and the Press, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Volgagrad Film Festival Photographs, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Wesley South / Paul Robeson Memorial, Undated (Box 35, Audiocassette 756_070)
  - Willie McGee, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin Steelworkers Strike, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Works Progress Administration - Federal Theatre Project, 1938-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Writers' Board for World Government, circa 1950 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Writing Leaflets, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)